https://www.rodeoticket.com/privacy-policy

Log In
Rodeo Ticket Privacy Policy
Rodeo Ticket
As of: June 20, 2018
We understand the value of your privacy and strive to protect it. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Race Registration Online, LLC dba Rodeo Ticket
(“Rodeo Ticket”, “we”, “us”, “our”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses your Personal Information (as defined below) through your use of the website http://rodeoticket.com/ (the “Site”). Please note that for the purpose of EU data protection laws, Rodeo Ticket is a “data controller” (the entity responsible for, and which controls the processing of, your Personal Information collected through the Site).
Personal Information
We may collect the following “Personal Information” from you: your name, email address, residential address, telephone number, IP address, purchase history and social media account information, including Facebook and Instagram that you provide to us when using the Site or communicating with us, gender, date of birth and payment card information. We collect your Personal Information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our Site, register on the Site, place an order, fill out a form, respond to a survey, or in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. We will collect your Personal Information only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply Personal Information, but please note that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal Information
We may collect non-personal information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personal information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers used and other similar information.
How we use Personal Information
We collect and use your Personal Information for the purpose of conducting our business and pursuing our legitimate interests, including for the following purposes:
To run and operate our business and Site: We will use your Personal Information to provide you with Rodeo Ticket
products, services and technologies that you purchase. We may also use your Personal Information to display content on the Site correctly.
To improve customer service: Personal Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience: We may use your Personal Information in the aggregate to understand how Site users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site, products and services: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. We may also use your Personal Information for auditing or research and analysis to improve Rodeo Ticket
products, technologies and services.
To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature: To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.
To send periodic emails: We may send you information and updates pertaining to your order or event registration. We may also send you information about the Site, promotions or upcoming events that may be of interest to you and respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
To facilitate event services you have requested: In some cases, your Personal Information is shared with third-party entities who explicitly partner with a specific Event Organizer (as defined below) to which you have voluntarily given your Personal Information and only to assist in that specific Event Organizer’s event operations.
How we protect your Personal Information
We implement appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your Personal Information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. For example, we use security measures such as data encryption, SSL secure link usage and password protection where applicable.
Sharing your Personal Information
We may share your Personal Information with others, such as our affiliates, government entities and regulatory bodies, those with whom you have requested us to share information, contractors and service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business, including, for example, companies that provide us with technical support and assistance concerning this website, our suppliers, and other third parties who facilitate delivery of the products you have purchased. We require third parties who perform services for us to agree to treat your Personal Information confidentially and securely and only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf. We may also share your Personal Information with a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Rodeo Ticket’s assets.
Please note that when you register for an event on our Site, such event is hosted by a third-party event organizer (“Event Organizer”). Personal Information you provide when registering for an event is shared with the event’s Event Organizer.
We do not control, and we are not responsible for, how Event Organizers use your Personal Information. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of the Event Organizer when registering for an event to understand how your Personal Information may be used by such Event Organizer.
Electronic newsletters
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or you may contact us using the contact information below.
Retention of Personal Information
We retain your Personal Information for as long as you remain a customer and thereafter only for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law, including to fulfill a legal obligation.
External Links and Third party websites
You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. Such external links and websites are operated by third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Once you have left our Site, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of Personal Information you provide on other websites. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and privacy policy. You should exercise caution and review the privacy policy of any website you visit.
Cookies
Our Site uses “cookies” to enhance your experience while using the Site. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that certain Site features may not function properly.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our Site may be delivered to you by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
“Do Not Track” disclosure
Certain web browsers may allow you to enable a “do not track” option that sends signals to the websites you visit indicating that you do not want your online activities tracked. This is different than blocking cookies as browsers with the “do not track” option selected may still accept cookies. We currently do not honor “do not track” signals. If we do so in the future, we will update this Privacy Policy accordingly.
Children’s Privacy
Rodeo Ticket
facilitates registration for various events, some of which allow participants under the age of 13. We require a date of birth for all registration entries. We require parental or guardian consent for children under the age of 13 to register on our Site. If we learn that we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental or guardian consent, we will delete that information.
Site visitors from outside the United States
Rodeo Ticket is located, and this Site is hosted, in the United States. If you are using the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that any Personal Information you share with us will be stored and processed in the United States where we locate and operate our servers and databases. By voluntarily sharing your Personal Information with us, you understand that your Personal Information will be stored and processed in the United States.
Your rights
Individuals in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) have certain data subject rights that may be subject to limitations and restrictions. These rights include the right to: (i) request access to and rectification or erasure of their Personal Information; (ii) obtain restriction of processing or object to processing of their Personal Information; and (iii) ask for a copy of their personal information to be provided to them or a third party in a machine readable format. If you wish to exercise one of the above-mentioned rights, please send us your request to the contact details set out below. Individuals in the EEA also have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of their Personal Information with their local data protection authority.
California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, you may contact us as described below.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at
Follow Rodeo Ticket!
Log In
Copyright © 2020 RODEOTICKET.COM
All rights reserved.
